McConnell, John W., Papers /3052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John W. McConnell Papers
1946-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McConnell, John W.
/3052
61.5 cubic feet
61.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Arbitration cases, subject files, ILR course materials, and ILR Dean records.
3078808
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 13, 2004
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5961: John W. McConnell Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States --Cases.; McConnell, John Wilkinson, 1907-; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations-- Faculty.
3078808
- R.P. Adams Co., Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4447, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  8/13/1975
- Addison, NY, Central School District vs. Addison Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  no award, 7/16/74
- Addison, NY, Central School District vs. Addison Teachers Association, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  7/16/1984
- Afro-American Co. of Baltimore vs. United Paperworkers of America, Local 111 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  no award
- Afro-American Co. of Baltimore vs. United Paperworkers of America, Local 111, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  no award, Feb. 1953?
- Airco Industrial Cases vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 25, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  12/26/1970
- Albany, NY, City of, vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 66, Local 1961, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  3/23/1976
- Ethan Allen Creamery vs. Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), New England Joint Board (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Allied Chemical co., Industrial Chemicals Division, vs. Allied and Technical Workers, Local 12457, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  3/9/1972
- Allied Chemical Co. vs. Brewery Workers, Local 12330, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  4/22/1975
- Altman Bottling co. vs. Brewery Workers, Local 1164, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  4/10/1978
- American Biltrite Corp. vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastics Workers, Local 25, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  1/27/1972
- American Optical, Scientific Instrument Division, vs. United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Local 222, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  1/20/1977
- American Standard, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 897, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  8/3/1971
- American Standard, Inc. Plumbing and Heating Division, vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4537, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  11/7/1973
- Amesbury, MA, School Committee vs. Amesbury Classroom Teachers Association, American Federation of Teachers, Local 1033, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  10/27/1973
- Amsterdam, NY, Greater School District, vs. Amsterdam Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  3/21/74, no award
- Amsterdam, NY, Greater School District, vs. Amsterdam Teachers Association (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Anaconda American Brass Co. vs. International Union of Mine, Mill, and Shelter Workers, Local 593, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  1/14/1963
- Anaconda American Brass Co, vs. United Automobile Workers, Local 1078 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Anaconda American Brass Co. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6445, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  4/2/1973
- Armstrong Cork Co. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 701, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  1/16/1974
- Arrow Automotive Industries vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1596, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  1/3/1974
- Auburn, NY, City of, vs. International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 1446 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Avoca, NY. Central School District, vs. Avoca Central School Teachers Association (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ayer, MA. School Committee vs. Ayer Teachers Association (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Barrington, RI, School Committee, vs. Barrington Teachers Association (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Redford, NH, School Board vs. Bedford Teachers Association (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bellingham, MA, Town of, vs. Bellingham Police Association, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  9/10/1976
- Biddeford, ME, Board of Education vs. Biddeford Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  1/23/1973
- Big Cs Discount Stores vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Local 328 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bison Painting and Decorating Corp. vs. Painters District Council # 4., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  11/28/1977
- Bloomfield, CT. Board of Education vs. Bloomfield Education Association, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  9/20/1970
- Boise Cascade Containers Corp. vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Nutmeg Local 745, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  no award, April 1974
- Bonwit Teller, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Local 187, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  9/7/1974
- Boston Edison Co. vs. Boston Edison Professional Unite # 386, Utility Workers of America, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  10/12/1972
- Boston Edison Co. vs. Utility Workers of America, Local 369, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  10/2/1970
- Boston Edison Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 369, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  5/10/1972
- Boston Gas Co. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12003, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  no date ( March 1974?)
- Boston Edison Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 369, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  includes correspondence re the set up of an arbitration hearing (4/8/71 is most recent correspondence to date.)
- Boston Edison Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 369, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  includes current and related correspondence (5/10/72)
- Boston Edison Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 369, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  includes transcript, hearing notes, correspondences, and award. (3/4/75)
- Boston Edison Co. vs. Utility Workers of America, Local 369, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  includes company's opening statement and correspondence (folder dated 6/9/70)
- Boston Edison Co. vs. UWUA, Local 639, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  includes award, exhibit, correspondence (10/22/63)
- Boston Gas Company vs. International Union of District 50 Allied & Technical Workers, Locals 12004 and 12118, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  6/9/1971
- Boston Herald American/ Advertisers Division the Hearst Corp vs. The Newspaper Guild of Greater Boston, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  4/11/1974
- Boston Herald American vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Boston, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  10/23/79?
- Boston, School Committee of the City of vs. The Boston Teachers Union, Local 66, of the American Federation of Teachers (Box 3, Folder 11)
  no date but does include award
- Boston, School Committee of the City of vs. The Boston Teachers Union, Local 66, of the American Federation of Teachers (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Boston, School Committee of the City of vs. The Boston Teachers Union, Local 66, of the American Federation of Teachers (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Boston, School Committee of the City of vs. The Boston Teachers Union, Local 66, of the American Federation of Teachers (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Boston, School Committee of the City of vs. The Boston Teachers Union, Local 66, of the American Federation of Teachers (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Bradford Central School District vs. Bradford Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  6/21/1976
- Brattleboro Town School District, the Joint Boards of School Directors, Brattleboro Union High School District, Guilford Town School District vs. the Windham Southeast Education Association (Box 4, Folder 6)
  no date, McConnell on fact finding board
- Brewer- Titchener Corp vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1774, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  8/28/1976
- Bridgewater State College vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1067, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  7/11/1972
- Bristol School Committee of Bristol, Rhode Island vs. Bristol Education Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  5/27/1976
- Bristol School Committee vs. Bristol Education Association, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  11/10/1978
- Bristol School Committee vs. Bristol Education Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  11/12/1976
- Bristol School Committee vs. United Steel Workers of America, Local 14434, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  11/16/1978
- Bristol School Committee vs. Bristol Education Association, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  2/21/1974
- Bristol School Committee vs. Bristol Education Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  9/1/1976
- Brockway Corporation ( Watertown, NY) vs. Times Mechanical Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  4/27/1976
- Bronson Co. Homer D. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5104, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  6/7/1978
- Broome County, New York vs. Civil Service Employees Association ( CSEA), Broome County Unit, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  2/9/1974
- Brown University, Providence, Rhode Island vs. Service Employees International Union ( SEIU) Local 134 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Burlington, Town of, Massachusetts vs. International Brotherhood of Police Officers, Local 314, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  6/19/1978
- Burlington, City of, Vermont vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1343, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  8/14/1973
- Burlington, City of Vermont, vs. AFSCME, Local 1343, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  8/8/1972
- Burt Co. Inc. F,N, Buffalo NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 76, Local 330, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  7/17/1975
- Butterfield Division, UTD Corporation, Litton Industries vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1829, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  3/5/1973
- Butterfield Division, itton Industrial Products Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Border Lodge No. 1829, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  12/3/1975
- CR&L Company vs. Amalgamated Transport Union, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  6/8/1972
- Capital District Transportation Authority, Albany NY vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1321 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  no date
- Carter Pill Driving Inc. Nat Mass. vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local Union 56, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  2/5/1973
- Carthage Central School System vs. Carthage Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  5/15/1979
- Celluplastics Incorporated (Division of Brockway Glass Com, Nashua, NH) vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Union Local 875, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  4/7/1977
- Crane Co. Chapman Division vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 278 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Claremont Paper Mill (Division of Bermis Co.) vs. United Paper workers International, Local Union 177, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  5/21/1973
- Clarkstown Central School District. # 1 Board of Education vs. Clarkstown Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  5/30/1973
- Cleveland Electric Illuminating Company vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 270 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  no date or award
- Clinton Central School District vs. Clinton Teachers Association, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  1/7/1977
- Coca Cola Bottling Co, Braintree Plant vs. New England Joint Board of Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  12/12/1972
- Cohasset, Massachusetts School Committee vs. Cohasset Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  1/26/1974
- Pratt Whitney Small Tool Division of Colt Industries vs. United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 218, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  11/15/1974
- Columbine Rope Company vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1085, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  2/14/1976
- Columbia Mills, Incorporated vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 129, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  8/24/1962
- Concord, Massachusetts, Town of vs. Concord Fire-fighters Association, Local 1942 (Fact finding), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  10/28/1977
- Connecticut Education Association vs. Connecticut Education Association Professional Staff Organization, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  8/15/1977
- Connecticut, State of vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU District 1199, (Fact finding), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7-10)
  7/17/79 (award is in file folder 7)
- Connecticut, State of vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU District 1199 (Fact finding) continued from above (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Red Binder, Connecticut, State of vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU District 1199 (Fact finding) continued from above (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Package of Exhibits, Connecticut, State of vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU District 1199 (Fact finding) continued from above (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Copley Playa Hotel, Boston Massachusetts vs. Hotel, Restaurant, Institutional Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 250 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Corning, City of vs. Corning City Police, and Service Employees Association (Box 7, Folder 5)
  no award included in folder and no date
- Corning- Painted Post Area School District vs. Corning Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  2/5/1976
- Corning- Painted Post Area School District vs. Corning Teachers Association (only exhibit though) (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Courier Citizen Company, Cornell MA vs. Cornell Typographical Union, Local 310, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  9/12/1978
- Courier Express, Buffalo vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 41, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  4/5/1977
- Cranston, Rhode Island, School Committee of vs. Cranston Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  4/23/1974
- Cranston, Rhode Island, School Committee of vs. Cranston Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  6/28/1974
- Cranston School Committee vs. Cranston Association of Para-professionals, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  8/1/16/72 and addendum to award
- Cranston, The School Committee of vs. The Cranston Education Association, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  6/10/1976
- Cranston, The School Committee of vs. The Cranston Education Association, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  6/12/1976
- Cumberland, Rhode Island School Committee vs. The Cumberland Teachers Association (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Cumberland, Rhode Island School Committee vs. the Cumberland Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  6/4/1974
- Cumberland, Rhode Island School Committee vs. The Cumberland Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  2 awards, 7/26/74, 8/17/74
- Cumberland, Rhode Island School Committee vs. The Cumberland Teachers Association (Box 8, Folder 11)
  no date on rough copy of award
- Cumberland, Rhode Island School Committee vs. The Cumberland Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  10/20/1975
- Cummins Northeastern, Incorporated, Dedham, Massachusetts vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1898 of District 38, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  4/26/1971
- Cyprus Wine and Label Company, vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1875, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  7/17/1978
- Dairylea Cooperative, Incorporated vs. Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 338 of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  12/12/1977
- Danbury Board of Education, Danbury, Connecticut vs. Danbury Education Association, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  3/8/1976
- Danville Board of School Directors vs. Danville Teachers Association (Box 9, Folder 3)
  no award and no date
- Darien Board of Education vs. Darien Education Association, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  3/21/1975
- Dartmouth, Massachusetts School Committee vs. Dartmouth Teachers Association (Box 9, Folder 5)
  no award, no date
- Davol, Incorporated of Cramton Rhode Island vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 911, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  6/3/1975
- Davol, Incorporated of Providence and Cramton Rhode Island vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 911, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  1/3/1976
- Davol, Incorporated of Providence and Cramton Rhode Island vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 911, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  12/29/1975
- Dresser Manufacturing Division, Bradford, PA and International Association of Machinists Lodge 1644 and International Brotherhood of Black Smiths, Drop Forgers and Helpers, Local 647, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  no date on award, though hearing was held on 2/5/47
- Dresser Industries, Transportation Division of Depew, NY vs. United Steel Workers of America, Local 5875, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  9/12/1973
- Dresser Industries Transportation Equipment Division, Depew, NY vs. United Steel Workers of America, Local 1630 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  no date on copy of award
- Dresser Industries, Inc. Dresser Clark Division, Olean, New York vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4601, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  1/5/1976
- Dutchess Community College, State University of New York, Poughkeepsie, New York vs. Dutchess United Educators, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  5/1/1975
- East Greenwich Rhode Island School Committee vs. East Greenwich Education Association, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  1/3/1977
- East Hartford Board of Education vs. East Hartford Education Association, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  9/7/1971
- East Providence Rhode Island School Committee vs. East Providence Education Association, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  9/8/1977
- Eastern Company, Alley Foundries Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1558, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  5/22/1978
- Eastern Containers Corporation of Springfield Massachusetts vs. International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, Local 284, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  1/18/1977
- Eastern Plastics Corporation vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1718, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  11/17/1973
- Eden Central School District vs. Eden Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  7/24/1975
- Elmira City School District vs. UNISERV, The Classroom Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  11/13/1972
- Enfield, Connecticut Board of Education vs. Enfield Teachers Association, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  11.25.77
- Ernst Construction Company, a Division of Ernst Steel Co vs. Shopmens Local 576 of International Association of Bridge Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  9/5/1978
- Fairport, NY Central School District vs. Fairport Education Association (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Falconer, NY Board of Education vs. Falconer Education Association (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Falconer, NY Board of Education vs. Falconer Education Association, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  9/21/1974
- Fall River, MA School Committee vs. Fall River Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  5/23/1972
- Fall River, MA School Committee vs. Fall River Educators Association, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  6/7/1976
- Falmouth, MA School Committee vs. Falmouth Educators Association, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  8/18/1973
- Falmouth, MA School Committee vs. Falmouth Educators Association, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  11/17/1977
- Falmouth, MA School Committee vs. Falmouth Educators Association (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Farrand Optical Corporation, Incorporated vs. United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 475, CIO, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Farrel Co. vs. United Steelworkers of America (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Farrel Co. vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Farrel Co. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3571, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  3/16/1976
- Fayetteville-Manlius, NY Central School District vs. Fayetteville-Manlius Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Fernandes Supermarkets, Incorporated, vs. Southeast Independent Employees Association, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  3/21/1974
- Fernandes Supermarkets, Inc. vs. Southeast Independent Employees Association, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  1/16/1973
- First National Stores, Incorporate, vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 2, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  9/6/1977
- First National Stores, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 2, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Firchburg Gas and Electric Light Company vs. Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England, Local 340, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  7/2/1974
- Fitchburg Paper Co. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 16, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Foster-Wheeler Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Dansville Lodge No. 1665, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  no date (1962?)
- Foster-Wheeler Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Dansville Lodge No. 1665, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  12/13/1972
- Foster-Wheeler Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists, Dansville Lodge No. 1665, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  9/15/1974
- Fountain Plating, Inc. vs. United Automobile and Agricultural Implement Workers Union (UAW) Local 1596, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  5/7/1974
- Fountain Plating Incorporate vs. UAW Local 1596, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  7/28/1976
- Framingham, Massachusetts, town of, vs. Framingham Police Association, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  8/9/1976
- Framingham Massachusetts, town of. Vs. Massachusetts Laborers International Union, Local 1156, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  6/7/77 / 10/10/77
- Friendship, BY, Central School District vs. Friendship Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  9/17/1976
- Fulton-Montgomery (NY) Community College vs. Fulmont Association of College Educators, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  5/16/1977
- Keith Fulton & Sons, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 379, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Gannett Co., Inc. vs. Rochester Pressmens and Assistants Union No. 36, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Guy Gannett Publishing Co. vs. Portland Newspaper Guild, Local 128, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  no date (1971?)
- Gates-Chili, NY Central School District vs. Gates-Chili Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Gates-Chili, NY Central School District vs. Gates-Chili Teachers Association, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  10/25/1978
- O.Z./ Geduen Co. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2321, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- General Dynamics, Electric Boat Division, vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 1871, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- General Mills, Inc., O. Cel-O Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 13833, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  12/11/1974
- Genesee County (NY) Community College vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  4/20/1978
- Georgia-Pacific Corp,. Woodland Division vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 2400, International Association of Machinists, Local 1490; and International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 330, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  12/24/1973
- Georgia-Pacific Corporation vs. International Association of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 27, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  10/11/1972
- Georgia-Pacific Corp., Woodland Division, vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 330, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  12/1/1974
- Globe-Union Inc. vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW) Local 1271, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  12/7/1977
- Goodall-Sanford Inc., Reading Division, vs. Local Union 22750, AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  10/26/1972
- General Tire and Rubber Company., Reading Division, vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Local 971, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  12/17/1975
- Grand Island Central School District vs. Grand Island Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  8/14/1975
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company (A&P) vs. Amalgamated Food Workers, AMC local 10, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  7/21/1978